[Music]
This information is our opinion only and
not financial advice. Please do your own research before making any decisions.
We are not liable for any profits or losses.
ICCI Lord General
Insurance Company has released its latest
shareholding report, which
covers the quarters and first half of the financial year ending September 30, 2024.
This report
provides detailed information on the company's shares, including those held by promoters,
promoter groups, foreign investors, public
investors, and government entities.
Promoters' shareholding declined from 51.8% in June 2024
to 51.6% in September 2024. This decline indicates
that promoters' control over the company has weakened during this time period. The
percentage of public health shares held declined from
6.97% in June 2024 to 6.86% in September 2024.
This decline clearly indicates that the
public's stake in the company has declined during this time period. There has been a
slight decline in the shareholding of domestic institutional investors.  From June 2024 to
September 2024, which shows that
domestic institutions have decreased their stake
by -0.56. FIIs (Foreign
Institutional Investors) increased their
shareholding from 20.33 in June 2024
to 24.75 in September 2024. This shows that
foreign institutions have increased their interest in the company
by 0.82. Let us
look at the investor statistics
which
can be the reason for fluctuations in the shareholding pattern. Promoters'
shareholding has decreased from 51.81 in June 2024
to 51.66 in September 2024.
This decline shows that
promoters' control over the company has weakened during this time period.
Percentage of Public Health Shares has decreased from 6.97 in June 2024
to 6.86 in September 2024.  It is
clear from this decree that the
public's stake in the company has declined during this time period. There was a
slight decrease in the shareholding of domestic institutional investors from
June 2024 to September 2024, which shows
that domestic institutions have
decreased their stake by -0.56. FI
Foreign Institutional Investors
increased their shareholding from 23.9 in June 2024 to 24.75 in September 2024. This shows that
foreign institutions have increased their interest in the company
by 0.82. III
Bank Limited did
not hold any shares in the previous quarter, but
in the current quarter they hold 51.66 shares.
III Bank Limited used to
hold 51 shares in the previous quarter, but in this
quarter they have
exited the company. Mutual Fund Slash
decreased its stake by 15.0 in the previous quarter.
This shows a stake difference of -0.12 in the corresponding quarters.
UTI
Mutual Fund through various schemes has decreased its
stake to 1.03 from 1.17 in the previous quarter.
This
shows a stake difference of -0.14 in the corresponding quarters.
Nippon Life Mutual Fund through
various schemes saw an increase in stake holding in the latest quarter,
which saw an uptick of 0.06.
ICICI Prudential Mutual Fund through
various schemes has decreased its stake to 2.51
from 2.94 in the previous quarter.
This shows a
stake difference of -0.43 in the corresponding quarters.
SBI Mutual Fund through various schemes has decreased
its stake to 3.39
from 4.16 in the previous quarter. This shows a stake difference of -0.77 in the
corresponding quarters.
In the latest quarter, Alternate
Investment Funds have increased their stake to 3.39 from 4.16 in the previous quarter.  There was an increase in stake holding, with an
uptake of 0.06%.
Insurance companies have decreased their
stake from 1.13% in the previous quarter to
0.62%. This
shows a difference of -0.51% stakes in the consecutive quarters.
In the latest quarter, Provident Funds and Pension
Funds saw an increase in stake holding, with an
uptake of 0.01%. Rajasthan
Global Securities Private Limited entered the
company with 1.22% shares in the current quarter,
whereas in the previous quarter
they held % shares. There was
a notable increase in the stake holding of Foreign Portfolio Investors Category I in the previous quarter. There was a
significant
increase of 0.66% in their stake holding. There was a notable increase in the
stake holding of Government Pension Fund Global in the previous quarter. There was a significant
increase of
0.01% in their stake holding. There was a
significant increase of 0.01% in the
stake holding of Foreign Portfolio Investors Category II in the previous quarter.
Noteworthy Increase Stock Viewed
Subscribe to the channel for latest news updates and like and share the video